miniclip-games.net 2007-09-19

# Miniclip Free Games - Online Arcade Games

GENERAL

The games provided by this website are considered to be from the public domain, e.g. they are widely found on many other gaming sites and comply with second party site's policies. We try our best to give as much credit back to those authors/owners/organisations as possible.  
But if you believe such a game should not be featured on our website, please contact the webmaster and we shall arrange to take off the game as soon as possible. Usually within 24-48 hours.

GUESTS

We do not collect any personal information on this website. However, our web server logs all visitor information and we use this for statistical purposes. 

MEMBERS

Your profile information will be available to anyone who chooses to view it. Do not put sensitive personal information in your profile. We will not share your e-mail address with anyone. It will be used to send you site news and newsletters. You may opt-out of these at any time once you've logged into the site. 

* Registration.  
When you register, Miniclip-Games.net asks for your e-mail address, a user selected user name, and other information. Once you are a registered user you can update your profile and may be able to provide additional preferential information (e.g. a member name, a nickname, and certain user preferences). 
* Cookies.  
A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored with your Web browser for record-keeping purposes and to help us provide better service to you. Your browser has options to accept, reject, or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. We use cookies to save your password (in an encrypted format) on your machine so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and track your downloads and purchases from the Miniclip-Games.net Site. 
* Links to Other Sites.  
The Miniclip-Games.net Site contain links, including banner and other ads, to other Web sites. Miniclip-Games.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. The Miniclip-Games.net Site may also link to Web sites that feature Miniclip-Games.net trademarks and names along with trademarks and names of other companies. You should look at the privacy policy on that co-branded 
* Acceptance of Privacy Policy.  
Your use of the Miniclip-Games.net Site, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy. By using the Miniclip-Games.net Site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of the Miniclip-Games.net.
